Planning a family trip means thirty hours
lost across review sites, maps, and forums —
and you still aren't sure.
HotelZippo replaces all of it
with one conversation.
You just talk. Tell it
who's travelling and where —
a vegetarian family heading to Phuket
with two kids and grandparents —
and it asks the right questions, building a
complete picture of what your family needs.
Then it delivers one confident pick —
backed by family reviews synthesised by AI,
not a wall of links.
And it never buries a dealbreaker.
When a hotel has a real problem, the warning
is right there, above everything else.
Honesty over polish.
Save it, and book it — straight through.
From a single question to a booking
you can trust, in under a minute.
HotelZippo. The family travel concierge.